pad2pad.com 2006-12-07

# Privacy Statement - Free PCB design software - Printed circuit boards manufacturing

|  | 

Newcomers   
  
---  
  |  | 

Demo                
  
  |  | 

Free Download      
  
  |  | 

FAQ                  
  
  |  | 

Capabilities  
  
  |  | 

Glossary  
  
  |  | 

Pricing  
  
Pad2Pad Users   
  
  |  | 

New in 1.7.5  
  
  |  | 

Order Status  
  
  |  | 

Support           
  
  |  | 

Suggestions    
  
Company   
  
  |  | 

About Pad2Pad       
  
  |  | 

Pad2Pad in Media  
  
  |  | 

Links                
  
  |  | 

Tell a Friend       
  
  |  | 

Contact Us       
  
Links:

Privacy Statement

Pad2Pad.com respects your privacy choices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.

Pad2Pad.com encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Below is a summary of Pad2Pad.com's online privacy policy.

E-mail addresses

Pad2Pad.com is sensitive to the improper use of conventional mailings and e-mailings. We do not supply e-mail addresses to third parties. We occasionally use e-mail addresses to notify customers of relevant new software updates but we keep such use to a minimum - normally less than four messages per year. If you wish to remove your e-mail address from our files reply with REMOVE in the Subject field or write to [support@pad2pad.com](mailto:support@pad2pad.com).

Security measures.

We protect the personal information you share with us. For example, if you make an online order with us, we encrypt your credit card number.

Authorized third parties may need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We limit such third parties in their access and use of your personal information.

Policy updates:

All updates to this policy will be posted here. Last update: March 10, 2004.

Questions?

Please send any questions or comments on our privacy practices to [support@pad2pad.com](mailto:support@pad2pad.com).

Pad2Pad.com is committed to user privacy in our products and services.

|
